comedywildlifephoto.com 2019-12-17

# The Affinity Photo People's Choice Award :: Comedy Wildlife Photography Awards - Conservation through Competition

This privacy policy sets out how the Comedy Wildlife Photography Awards uses and protects any information that you give the Comedy Wildlife Photography Awards when you use this website, or interact with us in any other way.

The Comedy Wildlife Photography Awards is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

The Comedy Wildlife Photography Awards may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 24th May 2018.

## The Comedy Wildlife Photography Awards

We are a Conservation minded wildlife photography competition.

Our registered address is:

65 Woodbridge Road, Guildford, Surrey, GU1 4RD, UK

You can contact us by writing to that address or by emailing us at [info@comedywildlifephoto.com](mailto:info@comedywildlifephoto.com)

## What we collect

Our legal basis for processing personal data is: Consent by entering the competition and / or signing up to the newsletter.

## We may collect the following information:

•    Name  
•    Contact information including email address  
•    Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers  
•    Your emails to us and other information that you give us in relation to the work that we perform for you

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

•    We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
•    We may send emails concerning the provision of any products or services that we supply to you, such as website service alerts, new features and the like.  
•    We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
•    From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online, or by any other method.

## How we use cookies on our website

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive or other data storage device. Once you agree, the file is added. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Our websites use cookies which are essential to the operation of the site, and which store the basic preferences of the user (e.g. the user’s choice whether or not to accept cookies).

We may also use cookies to track the use of our websites (e.g. to identify which pages are being used). This can include the use of Google Analytics and other 3rd party services. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our websites in order to tailor them to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

We may also use 3rd party cookies to help us present our visitors with more targeted information using services such as Facebook advertising.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website and service by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies using the slide-up panel at the bottom of our website. You can change your preferences at any time by clicking on the Cookies link in the footer which will redisplay the slide-up panel.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information for marketing purposes by opting out of such communications.

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us or emailing us via the Contact link on our website.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you by writing to us or emailing us via the contact page on our website.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

We acknowledge that you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner's Office in the United Kingdom if you are unhappy with the way we have collected, stored or used your personal information.
